Guide to the Rice University Early Land Deeds, Contracts and Related Records, 1830-1969 UA 222
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Rice Land Deeds, 1830-1966; 144825; 39 Linear Feet
  - Texas Counties, 144826
    - Blanco County, 145385
      - George Alexander Survey, Blanco Co., 1902-1916, 145388 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Sale, 469 acres in George Alexander Survey to J.R. Gipson, Blanco Co., 1916-1917, 145387 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Sale, 368 acres in George Alexander Survey to Charles and Scott Klett, Blanco Co., 1916-1917, 145386 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Brazos County, 145380
      - A.D. Lancaster Survey, Brazos Co., 1884-1938, 145384 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Right-of-way, sale in A.D. Lancaster Survey to Brazos Co., 1933, 145383 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Sale, 634 acres in A.D. Lancaster Survey to G.B and A.C. Adams, Brazos Co., 1941, 145382 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Lease, 633 acres in A.D. Lancaster Survey to Emmett Holland, Brazos Co., 1939, 145381 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Callahan County, 145375
      - Morgan L. Smith Survey, Callahan Co., 1908, 1917, 145379 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Sale, 469 acres in Morgan Smith Survey to J.H. Coats, Callahan Co., 1944, 1948, 145378 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Lease, 369 acres in Morgan Smith Survey to A.E. Baker, Callahan Co., 1937, 145377 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Morgan L. Smith Survey, Callahan Co., 1859-1947, 145376 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Dallas County, 145368
      - Deeds for Miller Switch new county road, Dallas Co., 1910, 145374 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence concerning D. McFarland and Robinson Smith Survey's, Dallas Co., 1907, 145373 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - D. McFarland Survey, Dallas Co., 1894-1915, 145372 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Receipts, correspondence concerning Dallas County abstracts, 1913, 145371 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Sale, 157 acres in McFarland and Smith Surveys to Mike H. Thomas, Dallas Co., 1913-1922, 145370 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 2 lots in City of Dallas to Albert Strang, Dallas Co., 1944, 145369 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Ellis County, 145363
      - Wesley Haigler Survey, abstract, Ellis Co., 1896, 145367 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Wesley Haigler Survey, Ellis County, 1844-1875, 1902-1922, 145366 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Sale, 135 acres on Trinity River Levee to Ellis County Levee, Improvement District 3, 1917, 145365 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Sale, 1392 acres in Wesley Haigler Survey to Charles E. Kooken, Ellis Co., 1918-1919, 145364 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Erath County, 145360
      - L.R. Owen Survey, Erath Co., 1853, 1877, 1891, 1908-1916, 145362 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Sale, 320 acres in L.R. Owens Survey to T.A. Nored in Erath Co., 1917-1922, 145361 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Falls County, 145355
      - J.G.W. Pierson Survey, Falls Co., 1870, 1885, 1908, 145359 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - S.W. White Survey, Falls Co., 1907-1909, 145358 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Sale, 200 acres in S.W. White League to C.C. McCollum, Falls Co., 1909, 145357 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Sale, 1290 acres in Pierson Survey to J.E. Master and W.R. Peters, Falls Co., 1910-1913, 145356 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Fayette County, 145353
      - Sale, 100 acres in J.P. McFarland Survey to J.W. Moore, Fayette Co., 1917, 145354 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Fort Bend County, 145351
      - Joseph D. Vermillion Survey, Fort Bend Co., 1920, 145352 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Freestone County, 145348
      - Sale 686 acres in N. Peck and M. Russell Leagues to L.R. Boyd Jr., Freestone Co., 1960, 145350 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Various deeds and title papers, Freestone Co., 1914-1916, 145349 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Galveston County, 145341
      - Galveston County lands, 1905-1911, 145347 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Sale of stock, Galveston Wharf Company, Galveston Co., 1918-1919, 145346 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Sale, 6 lots in Galveston to Robert Ingram, Galveston Co., 1909-1912, 145345 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Sale, 2 lots in Galveston to Walter E. Grover, Galveston Co., 1911, 145344 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Sale, 4 lots in Galveston to R.D. Bowen, Galveston Co., 1878, 1899-1913, 145343 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Dickinson Bayshore Addition to Florence Kennedy, Galveston Co., 1956, 1959, 145342 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Hardin County, 145337
      - Acquisition, 640 acres in Buffalo Bayou, Brazos and Colorado Railroad Company, Survey's from estate of W.R. Rice, Hardin Co., 1947, 145340 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Sale, timber, 106 acres in Buffalo Bayou, Brazos and Colorado Railroad Company Survey to J & S Lumber Company, Hardin Co., 1953, 145339 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Title papers, correspondence, plats etc. relating to the Charles Stewart Survey, Hardin Co., 1841, 1898-1942, 145338 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Harris County, 145136
      - Title papers and other documents concerning acquisition of property from Lockhart H. Wallis, Harris Co., 1910-1917, 145334 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Lockhart H. Wallis loan, 145820
        - Loan to Lockhart H. Wallis, bills and receipts, 1914-1917, 145336 (Box 10, Folder 2, Subfolder 1)
        - Loan to Lockhart H. Wallis, tax receipts, 1913-1917, 145335 (Box 10, Folder 2, Subfolder 2)
      - Correspondence, statements, notes, etc., concerning Lockhart H. Wallis, 1914-1919, 145333 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, statements, notes, etc., concerning Lockhart H. Wallis, 1917, 145332 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - James Blessing and William J. Brown Surveys, Harris Co., 1875-1892, 145331 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Johnathan Belden Survey, Harris Co., 1891-1900, 145330 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Various Harris County surveys, 1885-1915, 145320
        - Johnathan R. Black Survey, 1893-1915, 145329 (Box 11, Folder 1)
        - Cornelius Ennis Survey, 1892, 145328 (Box 11, Folder 2)
        - Mayberry B. Gray Survey, 1895, 145327 (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - T.W. House Survey, 1892, 1900, 145326 (Box 11, Folder 4)
        - J.B. Pier and Johnathan M. Swift Surveys, 1890-1896, 145325 (Box 11, Folder 5)
        - Houston Tap and Brazoria Railroad Company Survey, 1894, 145324 (Box 11, Folder 6)
        - Johnathan Walton Survey, 1885-1896, 145323 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - James Wells Survey, 1892, 145322 (Box 11, Folder 8)
        - McHenry Winburn Survey, 1892-1898, 145321 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Abstract, John Beldin Survey, Harris Co., 1893-1894, 145319 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Abstract, W. Hollingsworth Survey, Harris Co., 1907, 145318 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Abstract, John R. Black Survey, Harris Co., 1893, 145317 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - South Side Buffalo Bayou (SSBB), 217 Main St., Houston, Harris Co., 1843, 1892-1942, 145316 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - H. Tierswester Survey, Harris Co., 1914-1927, 145315 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Obedience Smith Survey, Nobles Addition, Harris Co., 1877, 1898, 1914, 145314 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Obedience Smith Survey, Harris Co., 1908-1924, 145313 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Property in block 503, Houston, Harris Co., 1922-1947, 145312 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Foreclosure papers, Braeswood Addition, Harris Co., 1928-1941, 145311 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Fairgrounds Addition, Harris Co., 1920-1935, 145310 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - A.C. Reynolds Survey, Harris Co., 1922-1933, 145309 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Smith Warehouse, North Side Buffalo Bayou (NSBB), Harris Co., 1905-1940, 145308 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Block 13, SSBB, Harris Co., 1907, 145307 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - R.B. Walling Conveyance, SSBB, Harris Co., 1923-1938, 145306 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - 11.5 acres of Johnathan Austin Survey, Harris Co., 1907-1940, 145305 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Block 72, SSBB, Harris Co., 1925-1933, 145304 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - 500 block of Milam, Houston, Harris Co., 1923-1936, 145303 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 7 acres in Billinghurst Subdivision to G. Roberts, Harris Co., 1921, 145302 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Sale, 2 lots in Conklin Addition to Harris Co., 1919, 145301 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Sale, 11.9 acres in John Donnelly Survey to John Hildebrandt, Harris Co., 1919, 145300 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Sale, 10 acres in Fairgrounds Addition to H.A. Paine, Harris Co., 1919-1928, 145299 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Sale, block 2, Hadley Home Reserve, SSBB, to W.E. Douglass, Harris Co., 1919-1921, 145298 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Sale, 2802 Smith St., Fairgrounds Addition to Eula Lee, 1919, 1927, 145297 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Sale, 9 acres in Reinerman Survey to G. Roberts, Harris Co., 1919-1921, 145296 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Sale, 20,000 Sq. Ft. of land, Tierwester Survey to J.F. Means, Harris Co., 1925, 145295 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Sale, right-of-way for Kuykendahl Rd., Donally Survey, Harris Co., 1925, 145294 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Sale, block 5, Senechal Addition, SSBB to Bernardo de George, Harris Co., 1923-1938, 145293 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Sale, 5 acres in Houston to HISD, Harris Co., 1926-1929, 145292 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Sale, 7 acres, Reinerman Survey to Gary Walker, Harris Co., 1926, 145291 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Sale, 26 acres of A.C. Reynolds Survey to Widee Realty, Harris Co., 1911-1934, 145290 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Sale, 9 acres of Obedience Smith Survey to W.D. Harden and Co., Harris Co., 1925-1930, 145289 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Sale, 157 acres of Obedience Smith Survey to City of Houston, Harris Co., 1923-1924, 145288 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Sale, Acme Lumber Co. Tract, SSBB to A.C. Abell, Harris Co., 1908-1914, 145287 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Sale, 1 acre in S.M. Williams Survey to Howard Fields Lumber Co., Harris Co., 1919-1943, 145286 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Glenwood Cemetery to Trustees of Glenwood Cemetery, Harris Co., 1912, 145285 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Sale, timber rights in J.C. Donnelly Survey to Henry R. Fall, Harris Co., 1912, 145284 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 4 lots, Main @ Truxillo, SSBB to J.W. Metzler, Harris Co., 1923-1938, 145283 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Sale, 179 acres in M.B. Gray Survey to Houston Realty Syndicate, Harris Co., 1926-1956, 145282 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Acquisition, Downtown Realty Co., 508-510 Travis St., City of Houston, Harris Co., 1921-1945, 145281 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Acquisition, Maurice William and Family, 44 acres in A.C. Reynolds Survey, Harris Co., 1925-1940, 145280 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Acquisition, T.J. Beetles, 5 lots in Central Park Subdivision, SSBB, Harris Co., 1925-1949, 145279 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Acquisition, Boysen's Corporation, 8 lots SSBB, Harris Co., 1929-1940, 145278 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Acquisition, E.A. Hester, 2 lots Riverside Terrace, City of Houston, Harris Co., 1926-1934, 145277 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Conveyance, 2 lots SSBB, City of Houston from Texas Realty Investments Co., Harris Co., 1928-1933, 145276 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Right-of-way, sale in M.B. Gray Survey to Harris Co., 1935, 145275 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Right-of-way, sale in John Donnelly Survey to Harris Co., 1933-1935, 145274 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Right-of-way, sale in Obedience Smith Survey to City of Houston, Harris Co., 1936-1937, 145273 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Sale, 2407 Oakdale St, Houston, to S.H. Ware, Harris Co., 1934-1935, 145272 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 1 lot (Prairie @ LaBranch) SSBB to Ben Milam Properties, Harris Co., 1941, 145271 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Sale, 2 lots in Camp Logan Addition to G.T. Roberts, Harris Co., 1933-1936, 145270 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Sale, 1 acre in Obedience Smith Survey to Coastal Securities Co., Harris Co., 1934, 145269 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Sale, 6 acres in A.C. Reynolds Survey to Marguerite F. Serafino, Harris Co., 1939, 145268 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Sale, 10 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey to Glen McCarthy, Harris Co., 1935-1939, 145267 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Sale, 1 lot SSBB to L.L. Ridgway, Harris Co., 1940, 145266 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Sale, 4 lots (Dallas and Fannin streets) SSBB to A.T. Vineyard, Harris Co., 1940, 145265 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - 4 acres in A.C. Reynolds Survey to E.J. Hudson, Harris Co., 1940, 145264 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Sale, 9 lots (Baker St. Warehouse) NSBB, Harris Co., to State Warehouse Corp., 1937 & A.I. Luck, 1940, 145263 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Sale, 3 lots SSBB to Durrell Carothers, Harris Co., 1940, 145262 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Sale, 3 acres in A.C. Reynolds Survey to J.A. Phalen, Harris Co., 1939, 145261 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Sale, 4 lots SSBB to J. Weingarten, Inc., Harris Co., 1939, 145260 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Sale, timber on 1260 acres in J.C. Donnelly Survey to J.S. Hunt Lumber Co., Harris Co., 1929, 145259 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Sale, 44 acres in A.C. Reynolds Survey to Harris Co., 1939, 145258 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Sale, 3 acres in Obedience Smith Survey to W.E. White, Harris Co., 1937, 145257 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Sale, 8 acres in Obedience Smith Survey to City of Houston, Harris Co., 1914, 145256 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Sale, 1 lot (510 Milam St.) SSBB to Roy Paul & V.H. Brady, Harris Co., 1940, 145255 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Sale, 1476 acres in W.C. Sypert Survey to Conoco Ranch Company, Harris Co., 1940, 145254 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Sale, 30 acres in Obedience Smith Survey to to Richwood Corp., Harris Co., 1937, 145253 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Fairgrounds Addition to C.E. Pizzitola, Harris Co., 1938, 145252 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Exchange, 8850 Sq. ft., SSBB from M. Sandel, Harris Co., 1912-1913, 145251 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Acquisition, 1 lot in Southampton Court Addition from Eda Kauer, Harris Co., 1944-1947, 145250 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Acquisition, 1 lot in Southwood Addition from W.C. Nunn, Harris Co., 1946, 145249 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Acquisition, 1 lot in River Oaks Subdivision from Paul B. Pennington, Harris Co., 1938-1946, 145248 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Acquisition, 67 acres in D. Gregg Survey from Merchant & Planters Oil Co., Harris Co., 1942, 145247 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Acquisition, 83 acres in Reinerman Survey from various sellers, Harris Co., 1911-1945, 145246 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Acquisition, 1 lot in Sunset Place Addition from Lillian McIntyre Schneider, Harris Co., (no content), 145245 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Acquisition, 5 lots in Ryan Addition from Audrey Moody Ley, Harris Co., 1862, 1957-1962, 145244 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Acquisition, 3 lots SSBB from P.B. Timpson, Harris Co., 1947, 145243 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Acquisition, 4 lots SSBB from Gertrude C. McCraven, Harris Co., 1947, 1952, 145242 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Acquisition, 371 acres in Post Oak Gardens from Amy M. Bering, et al, Harris Co., 1943-1954, 145241 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Acquisition, 7 lots in Turner Addition from Banks & Mt. Vernon Realty Co., Harris Co., 1948, 145240 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Acquisition, 2 lots in Holton Subdivision, City of Bellaire, from Leonard Genusa, Harris Co., 1947, 145239 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Acquisition, 1 lot in Southampton Addition from Kitty Autry, Harris Co., 1946-1948, 145238 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Sale, 40 acres in John C. Donnelly survey to John Hildebrandt, Harris Co., 1914-1915, 145237 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Sale, 16 acres NSBB to F.F. Kendall, Harris Co., 1902-1925, 145236 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Sale, 49 acres in John Austin Survey to City of Houston, Harris Co., 1916, 1943, 145235 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Sale, 3 lots SSBB to J.B. Greenfield and Louis Rosenberg, Harris Co., 1946, 145234 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Sale, 1 lot (217 Main St.) SSBB to C.N. DeClaris, Harris Co., 1944, 145233 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Sale, 6 lots (67th & Ave. B) SSBB to Duester Realty, Harris Co., 1944, 145232 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Bellaire to Ruth C. Harrison, Harris Co., 1950, 145231 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Sale, 26 acres in M.B. Gray Survey to Kinkaid School, Harris Co., 1954, 145230 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Houston to Andrew Louis, Harris Co., 1950, 145229 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Houston to Roy V. Talmage, Harris Co., 1947, 145228 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Sale, 67 acres in D. Gregg Survey to Channel Industrial Properties, Harris Co., 1944, 145227 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Sale, 1 lot (Banks & Mt. Vernon) SSBB to S & W Realty, Harris Co., 1957, 145226 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Bellaire to Carl R. Wischmeyer, Harris Co., 1950, 145225 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Houston to Ruth Springfield King, Harris Co., 1940, 145224 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Sale, 5 lots SSBB to F.H. Maloney Co. Profit Sharing Trust, Harris Co., 1962, 145223 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Sale, 4 lots in McGregor's Blodgett Addition to Sate of Texas, Harris Co., 1958, 145222 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Sale, 1 lot (1706 Bolsover) in Houston to Henry I. Johnson, Harris Co., 1950, 145221 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Sale, 7 acres in A.C. Reynolds Survey to F.A. Hunter and William Kinkaid, Harris Co., 1944, 145220 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Sale, 8 lots (Harrisburg & 65th St.) in S.M. Williams Survey to R.W. Nix, Harris Co., 1944, 145219 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Sale, 4 lots SSBB to Southwest Wheel, Inc., Harris Co., 1943, 145218 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Sale, 1/2 acre in A.C. Reynolds Survey to Marguerite F. Serafino, Harris Co., 1943, 145217 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Sale, 1 lot (Congress Ave.) SSBB to Morris Mintz, Harris Co., 1944, 145216 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Sale, 3 acres in M.B. Gray Survey to Houston Lighting and Power, Harris Co., 1944, 145215 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Sale, Easement strip (15' x 129') in Pleasant W. Rose Survey to Houston, Harris Co., 1947, 145214 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Sale, 1 lot (3419 Locke Lane) in Houston to Madeleine Shindler, Harris Co., 1947-1949, 145213 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - Sale, 41 acres in John D. Taylor Survey to Kinkaid School, Harris Co., 1956, 145212 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Sale, 6 lots (Westmoreland) to John S. Dunn, Harris Co., 1959, 145211 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Sale, 10 lots in Ryon Addition to Southwestern Bell, Harris Co., 1959, 145210 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Sale, 37 acres in A.C. Reynolds Survey to S.N. Adams, Harris Co., 1949, 145209 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - Sale, 6 lots in Jesse Pruitt Survey to Ollie L. Thomas, Harris Co., 1957, 145208 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - Sale, 16 acres in M.B. Gray Survey to Houston, Harris Co., 1944-1945, 145207 (Box 16, Folder 39)
      - Sale, 1 lot in Post Oak Gardens to Augustana Lutheran Church, Harris Co., 1956, 145206 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      - Sale, 6 lots (Clay & Milam) to Daniel Boleman McDaniel, Harris Co., 1943, 145205 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      - Sale, Easements in M.B. Gray Survey to Houston, Harris Co., 1950, 1953, 145204 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      - Sale, 10 acres in M.B. Gray Survey to Norman E. Pharr, Harris Co., 1945, 145203 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      - Lease, 6400 block of Harrisburg Blvd. in S.M. Williams Survey to C.M. Dow, A.E. Slaczyk & B.F. St Cyr, Harris Co., 1937-1941, 145202 (Box 16, Folder 44)
      - Lease, 23 acres of A.C. Reynolds Survey to Frank Pierce, Harris Co., 1944, 145201 (Box 16, Folder 45)
      - Lease, 23 acres in A.C. Reynolds Survey to J.P. Serafino, Harris Co., 1946, 145200 (Box 16, Folder 46)
      - Lease, Service Station in Pleasant W. Rose Survey to Gulf Oil Corp., Harris Co., 1939-1961, 145199 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      - Lease, 179 acres in M.B. Gray Survey to E.H. Letke, Harris Co., 1937-1947, 145198 (Box 16, Folder 48)
      - Lease, 3904 Brandt St. (fully furnished) from Mrs. Philip Carson, 1918-1919 (For Dr. Lovett), 169950 (Box 16, Folder 49)
      - Lease, 15 acres on Westheimer in A.C. Reynolds Survey to Frank Pierce, Harris Co., 1944, 145197 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Lease, block at LaBranch and Prairie St., SSBB to Steve Homes, Harris Co., 1937, 145196 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Lease, 217 Main St., SSBB to Mrs. Ollie Thornton, Harris Co., 1928-1940, 145195 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Lease, 4702 Main St., SSBB to Greater Houston Motors, Joe Wilk, G.E. Caldwell & M.E. Plonsky, Harris Co., 1936-1955, 145194 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Lease, 2120 McKinney Ave., SSBB to Donald E. Barton & M.D. Burkett, Harris Co., 1937-1940, 145193 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Lease, building, San Jacinto @ Walker St., SSBB to D.M. Carothers, Harris Co., 1950, 145192 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Lease, 510 Travis St., SSBB to Austin Woolens, Harris Co., 1938, 145191 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Lease, 100 acre tract on Clear Lake, Clear Lake Ranch, Harris Co., 1964, 145190 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Lease, oil & gas, 1476 acres of William Sypert Survey to Standard Oil and Gas Co., Harris Co., 1943, 145189 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Lease, office space at 510 Travis St., SSBB to Margaret D. & Ralph Morgan, Harris Co., 1944, 145188 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Lease, office space at 508-510 Travis St., SSBB to United States of America, Harris Co., 1940-1941, 145187 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Lease, 500 block of Travis St., SSBB to J. Weingarten, Inc., Harris Co., 1938-1948, 145186 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Lease, 4 lots 4702 Main St., SSBB to Compton W. Nohl, Harris Co., 1943, 145185 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Lease, retail space, 1009 Congress Ave., SSBB to Morris Mintz, Harris Co., 1940, 145184 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Lease, 4 lots in MacGregor's Blodgett Addition, SSBB to J.W.E. Airey, Harris Co., 1942, 145183 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Lease, 5 lots in MacGregor's Blodgett Addition, SSBB to Clyde Austin, Harris Co., 1947, 145182 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Lease, 4 lots, 4702 Main St., SSBB to Robert Cohen, Harris Co., 1944, 145181 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Lease, 4 lots, 4702 Main St., SSBB to J. Hatcher Auto Co., 1946, 145180 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Lease, 4 lots, 4702 Main St., SSBB to Ulma Farrell, Harris Co., 1947, 145179 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Lease, shop facility, Central Park Addition to R.R. Ross, Harris Co., 1939, 145178 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Lease, 1 lot Central Park Addition to G.P. Thevenote, Harris Co., 1937-1938, 145177 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Lease, 4 lots, Central Park Addition to Economy Distributors, Inc., Harris Co., 1934, 145176 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Lease, 1 lot in P.W. Rose Survey to J.I. Keller & Theo. F. Keller, Harris Co., 1936, 145175 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Lease, 1 acre in P.W. Rose Survey to George P. Martin, Harris Co., 1944, 145174 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Lease, 10 acres in M.B. Gray Survey to C.L. Horacefield, Harris Co., 1942-1944, 145173 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Sale, 8 acres in Obedience Smith Survey from various sellers, Harris Co., 1908, 145172 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Sale, 6.5 acres in Obedience Smith Survey, City of Houston tax lawsuit, Harris Co., 1913, 145171 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Abstract, 325 acres in Pleasant W. Rose League and Labor, Harris Co., 1895, 145170 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Abstract, 100+ acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey - Encroachment lawsuit vs. Weber, Warnecke, League, et al., Harris Co., 1908-1922, 145169 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Abstract, 112 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey to David Hannah, Harris Co., 1909, 145168 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Abstract, 10 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey, Harris Co., 1905, 145167 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Abstract, 10 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey, Harris Co., 1906, 145166 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Abstract, 100 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey, Harris Co., 1906, 145165 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Abstract, 113 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey, Harris Co., 1908, 145164 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Abstract, 177 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey, Harris Co., 1909Abstract, 177 acres in P.W. Rose Survey, Harris Co., 1909, 145163 (Box 18, Folder 2)